Guide to the Archives Union File (AUF), Section 2: Boxes 64-126
Archives Union File (AUF), Section 2: Boxes 64-126
Kheel Center for Labor- Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
Archives Union File (AUF), Section 2: Boxes 64-126
6046
Kheel Center
388.2 linear ft.
Pamphlets, publications.
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
The Archives Union File is a collection of publications of United States labor unions. Included is information on the American Institute for Free Labor Development. The AUF collection consists largely of pamphlets and publications of unions, collected by the Kheel Center.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Due to the volume of material in this collection the finding aid has been divided into twelve sections.
Section 1: Boxes 1-63
Section 2: Boxes 64-126
Section 3: Boxes 127-191
Section 4: Boxes 192-256
Section 5: Boxes 257-319
Section 6: Boxes 319.1-378
Section 7: Boxes 379-442
Section 8: Boxes 443-506
Section 9: Boxes 507-571
Section 10: Boxes 572-635
Section 11: Boxes 636-699
Section 12: Boxes 700-704
Boxes 650-659 and 661-662 have not been inventoried at this time.
SUBJECTS
Names:
AFL-CIO --Archives; AFL-CIO. American Institute for Free Labor Development--Archives; AFL-CIO. Building and Construction Trades Dept.--Archives; AFL-CIO. Department of Economic Research--Archives; AFL-CIO. Education Department--Archives; AFL-CIO. Executive Council--Archives; AFL-CIO. Human Resources Development Institute--Archives; AFL-CIO. Industrial Union Department--Archives; AFL-CIO. Legislative Department--Archives; AFL-CIO. Public Employees Department--Archives; AFSCME --Archives; Air Line Pilots Association --Archives; Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union --Archives; Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union. Research Department--Archives; Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America --Archives; American Association of University Professors --Archives; American Federation of Government Employees --Archives; American Federation of Labor --Archives; American Federation of Musicians --Archives; American Federation of Teachers --Archives; American Federation of Television and Radio Artists --Archives; American Guild of Musical Artists --Archives; American Postal Workers Union --Archives; Association of Flight Attendants (U.S.) --Archives; Bakery, Confectionary and Tobacco Workers International Union --Archives; Coalition of Labor Union Women (U.S.) --Archives; Communication Workers Union --Archives; Communications Workers of America --Archives; Congress of Industrial Organizations --Archives; Federation of Westinghouse Independent Salaried Unions --Archives; Hotel & Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union --Archives; Illinois State AFL-CIO --Archives; Industrial Workers of the World --Archives; International Association of Bridge, Structural and Ornamental Iron Workers --Archives; International Association of Fire Fighters --Archives; International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers --Archives; International Brotherhood of Painters and Allied Trades --Archives; International Brotherhood of Teamsters --Archives; International Ladies' Garment Workers Union --Archives; International Ladies' Garment Workers Union. Educational Department--Archives; International Longshoremens and Warehousemens Union --Archives; International Typographical Union --Archives; International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers --Archives; International Union of North American Laborers --Archives; International Union, Allied Industrial Workers of America --Archives; International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America --Archives; International Union, United Automobile, Aircraft, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America --Archives; International Union, United Automobile, Aircraft, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America. Ford Dept. --Archives; International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers --Archives; Jewish Labor Committee (U.S.) --Archives; National Association of Postal Supervisors --Archives; National Maritime Union of America --Archives; National Writers Union (U.S.) --Archives; New York State AFL-CIO --Archives; New York State United Teachers --Archives; Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union --Archives; Screen Actors Guild --Archives; Service Employees International Union --Archives; Sheet Metal Workers International Union --Archives; Teamsters for a Democratic Union --Archives; Textile Workers Union of America --Archives; United Association of Journeymen and Apprentices of the Plumbing and Pipe Fitting Industry --Archives; United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America --Archives; United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers --Archives; United Glass & Ceramic Workers of North America --Archives; United Mine Workers of America --Archives; United Office and Professionals Workers of America --Archives; United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum and Plastic Workers of America --Archives; United Steelworkers of America --Archives; Utility Workers Union of America --Archives; Writer's Guild of America --Archives
Subjects:
Agricultural laborers--Labor unions; Airlines--Employees--Labor unions; Textile workers--Labor unions; Barbers--Labor unions; Building-service employees--Labor unions; Clothing workers--Labor unions; Construction workers--Labor unions; Automobile industry workers--Labor unions; Bakery employees--Labor unions; Transport workers--Labor unions; Fire fighters--Labor unions; Electricians--Labor unions; Plumbers--Labor unions; Teachers--Labor unions; Glassworkers--Labor unions; Restaurants--Employees--Labor unions; Postal service--Employees--Labor unions; Rubber industry and trade--Labor unions
Form and Genre Terms:
Pamphlets.; Publications
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
RELATED MATERIALS
Other sections of this collection:
6046: Archives Union File (AUF)
6046: Archives Union File (AUF), Section 1: Boxes 1-63
6046: Archives Union File (AUF), Section 3: Boxes 127-191
6046: Archives Union File (AUF), Section 4: Boxes 192-246
6046: Archives Union File (AUF), Section 5: Boxes 257-319
6046: Archives Union File (AUF), Section 6: Boxes 319.1-378
6046: Archives Union File (AUF), Section 7: Boxes 379-442
6046: Archives Union File (AUF), Section 8: Boxes 443-506
6046: Archives Union File (AUF), Section 9: Boxes 507-571
6046: Archives Union File (AUF), Section 10: Boxes 572-635
6046: Archives Union File (AUF), Section 11: Boxes 636-699
6046: Archives Union File (AUF), Section 12: Boxes 700-704
Boxes 650-659 and 661-662 have not been inventoried at this point.
Related Collections:
6046 mf: Archives Union File on Microfilm
CONTAINER LIST
- Air Line Pilots Association (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Historical: a story of the origin and progression of the Air Line Pilots Association and of its key figure and organizer, 1930-1944, 1945; Publication (Box 64, Folder 1)
    Language: English.
  - Item 2: ALPA, Publication (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: The ALPA story: a history and study of the background, functions, and organization of the Air Line Pilots Association, Intl., 1954; Publication (Box 64, Folder 1)
- Air Line Pilots Association, Publication (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Information Bulletin, 1967; Publication (Box 64, Folder 2)
    Notes: vol.18:no.51 (1967)
    Format: Publication
  - Item 2: Information Bulletin, 1968; Publication (Box 64, Folder 2)
    Notes: vol.19:no.6,13,15,23,20,31-33, 35 (1968)
  - Item 3: Information Bulletin, 1969; Publication (Box 64, Folder 2)
    Notes: vol.20:no.23 (1969)
- Air Line Pilots Association, Publication (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Air Line Pilots Association - Negotiating Committee bulletins and correspondence, 1957-1959 (Box 64, Folder 3)
- Air Line Pilots Association, Publication (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: The State of the Association -, 1955; Publication (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: miscellaneous publications for the Air Line Pilots Association, Publication (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Service Aloft, 1956; Publication (Box 64, Folder 4)
    Notes: Publication for flight attendants
  - Item 4: The why of the Air Line Pilots Association by David L. Behncke, 1955; Publication (Box 64, Folder 4)
    Notes: Memo
  - Item 5: Unity or Confusion, 1958; Publication (Box 64, Folder 4)
    Notes: Publication for Air Line employees
  - Item 6: Air Line Pilots Assoc., Int'l. - Financial Statement, Dec. 31,1954, Publication (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Item 7: Labors biggest wind by Wesley Price, 1952; Publication (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Item 8: The common man up in the air, 1954; Publication (Box 64, Folder 4)
    Author: Howard G. Kurtz
- Air Line Pilots Association, Publication (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Compilation of the actions of the Air Line Pilots Assoc., 1968; Publication (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Informational kit, Air Line Pilots Assoc., Int'l., 1962; Publication (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: Report of merger study committee, 1961; Publication (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: sample of ALPA News Bulletin, 1959; Publication (Box 64, Folder 5)
- Air Line Pilots Association, Publication (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: ALPA Policy Manual, 1975; Publication (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: ALPA's organization for safety, 1963; Publication (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: Group Insurance Program, 1972; Publication (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: Merger Policies, 1967; Publication (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Item 5: Phase III, 1970; Publication (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Item 6: miscellaneous publications for the Air Line Pilots Association, 1974-1978 (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Item 7: This is ALPA, Publication (Box 64, Folder 6)
- Air Line Pilots Association, Publication (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Local ALPA Press Relations, Publication (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Informational Kit for Air Line Pilots Assoc., 1965; Publication (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Press Releases for April 1961, Publication (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Union pamphlets, 1958; Publication (Box 65, Folder 1)
- Air Line Pilots Association, Publication (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Insurance report of Retirement and Insurance Committee, 1967-1968 (Box 65, Folder 2)
    Author: ALPA
    Notes: Press release
- Air Line Pilots Association, Publication (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: ALPA News, 1968; Publication (Box 65, Folder 3)
    Notes: vol.6:no.9, 12 (1968)
  - Item 2: Shop Talk, 1965; Publication (Box 65, Folder 3)
    Notes: vol.3:no.11 (1965)
  - Item 3: Shop Talk, 1966; Publication (Box 65, Folder 3)
    Notes: vol.4:no.1-7,9-11 (1966)
  - Item 4: Shop Talk, 1967; Publication (Box 65, Folder 3)
    Notes: vol.5:no.1-7,10 (1967)
  - Item 5: Shop Talk, 1968; Publication (Box 65, Folder 3)
    Notes: vol.6:no.1-2,7,9-12 (1968)
- Air Line Pilots Association, Publication (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Accord reached in airline strike, 1951-1954 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Air Co-Pilots' pay rise is backed..., 1951-1956 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Air Pilots strike ties up line today, 1949-1957 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Air strike cost mounts, 1951-1956 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: Air unions attack non-regular lines, 1949-1957 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: Airline talks due at Ithaca Sept. 30, 1951-1956 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Item 7: Deadlock persists in airline walkout, 1951-1956 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Item 8: Mediation scores in pilot-airline rift, 1949-1957 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Item 9: Mediators meet in air line strike, 1951-1954 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Item 10: Mediators strive to end air strike, 1951-1954 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Item 11: Mohawk requests mediator to act in wage dispute, 1949-1957 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Item 12: Pilot group asks air safety board, 1949-1957 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Item 13: Pilots assail plan for ten-hour runs, 1951-1956 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Item 14: Pilots avoid part of Florida route, 1949-1957 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Item 15: Pilots consider spread of strike, 1949-1957 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Item 16: Pilots end strike against American, 1949-1957 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Item 17: Pilots postpone airline walkout, 1951-1954 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Item 18: Pilots union says strike will go on, 1951-1954 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Item 19: Pilots urge safety measures, 1951-1956 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Item 20: Seizure possible in airline strike, 1951-1956 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Item 21: Strike again set by airline pilots, 1951-1954 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Item 22: Strike by pilots grounds all craft of United Airlines, 1951-1954 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Item 23: Strike by pilots ties up big airline, 1951-1954 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Item 24: Strike is averted on 5 big airlines, 1951-1954 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Item 25: Strike on airline a boon to rivals, 1951-1956 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Item 26: Talks suspended in airline strike, 1951-1954 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Item 27: Truman aloof now in air pilot strike, 1951-1956 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Item 28: Truman urges end of airline tie-up, 1949-1957 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Item 29: US proposes plan to halt air strike, 1949-1957 (Box 65, Folder 4)
- Air Line Pilots Association, Publication (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Report of training plans committee, 1968; Publication (Box 65, Folder 5)
- Northwest Airlines, Inc., Publication (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: In the United States Court of Appeals, for the Eighth Circuit, Nos. 16059-60, Civil: Air Line Stewards and Stewardesses Association, International, Appellant v. Northwest Airlines, Inc., Appellee, Court of Appeal from the United States District Court, Di, 1958; Publication (Box 66, Folder 1)
    Author: Northwest Airlines, Inc.
- Air Line Pilots Association, Publication (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: miscellaneous Press Releases, Memos, Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 66, Folder 2)
- Air Line Pilots Association, Publication (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Air line gives pay rises, 1951-1955 (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Airline union planned, 1951-1955 (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Union raps airline liquor serving, 1951-1955 (Box 66, Folder 3)
- Alliance for Labor Action, Publication (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: ALA Action, 1971; Publication (Box 66, Folder 4)
    Author: Alliance for Labor Action
    Notes: vol.2:no.1,3-7 (1971)
  - Item 2: To find answers to the urgent problems of our society, Action taken at the Founding Conference, 1969; Publication (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: ALA, Alliance for Labor Action, Publication (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Alliance for Labor Action, 1969; Publication (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: miscellaneous memos, Publication (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: The rise and fall of the Alliance for Labor Action (1968-1972), Publication (Box 66, Folder 4)
    Author: Karl F. Treckel
  - Item 7: ALA Action, 1970; Publication (Box 66, Folder 4)
    Notes: vol.1:no.1-3 (1970)
- Aluminum, Brick and Clay Workers International Union, Publication (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Resolutions, Aluminum, Brick and Clay Workers International Union, AFL-CIO: International Convention, Columbus, Ohio, July 20-24, 1981, Publication (Box 67, Folder 1)
    Author: Aluminum, Brick and Clay Workers International Union
- Aluminum Workers International Union, Publication (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Shop Stewards manual, Publication (Box 67, Folder 2)
    Author: Aluminum Workers International Union
- Aluminum Workers International Union, Publication (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Aluminum Facts, 1942; Publication (Box 67, Folder 3)
- Aluminum Workers International Union, Publication (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Resolutions, Aluminum Workers International Union, AFL-CIO: Fourteenth Biennial Convention, Kalispell, Montana, July 16-20, 1979, Publication (Box 67, Folder 4)
- Amalgamated Bank of New Yew York, Publication (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Report of the Directors of the Amalgamated Bank of New York to the stockholders at their Fourth Annual Meeting, January 18, 1927, Publication (Box 68, Folder 1)
    Author: Amalgamated Bank of New Yew York
  - Item 2: The Amalgamated Bank of New York: the labor bank that manages union funds, Publication (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: The story of a bank: the Amalgamated Bank of New York, 1923-1963, Publication (Box 68, Folder 1)
- Amalgamated Housing Corporation, Publication (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Biennial report, 1954-1955: a report on the realization of a dream, Publication (Box 68, Folder 2)
    Author: Amalgamated Housing Corporation
  - Item 2: 30 years of Amalgamated Cooperative housing, 1927-1957, 1958; Publication (Box 68, Folder 2)
- Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, Publication (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Amalgamated Life Insurance Company, Inc., Publication (Box 68, Folder 3)
    Notes: Copies of insurance policies
  - Item 2: Report for 1956 & 1957 (Box 68, Folder 3)
    Author: Amalgamated Insurance Fund
  - Item 3: The welfare program of the Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, 1954; Publication (Box 68, Folder 3)
    Author: William P. Gottlieb
- American Institute for Free Labor Development, Publication (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: A consensus in action the AIFLD, 1962-1967 (Box 68, Folder 4)
    Author: American Institute for Free Labor Development
  - Item 2: Aims, Objectives and Program, May 1962, Publication (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: ASINCOOP, 1962-1967 (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Books for Unionists, Quarterly bibliographical bulletin, 1962-1967 (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: En Marcha!, 1962-1967 (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: The Grace Log, 1962-1967 (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - Item 7: UA Journal, 1962-1967 (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - Item 8: miscellaneous informational flyers and pamphlets, 1962-1967 (Box 68, Folder 4)
- IADSL, Actualidades, Publication (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: IADSL, Actualidades, 1967-1968 (Box 68, Folder 5)
    Notes: Sept. 8,19,21; Nov. 28; dec. 12 (1967); Jan. 16, 24 (1968)
- American Labor Archive and Research Institute, Inc., Publication (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: miscellaneous pamphlets and correspondence, 1944; Publication (Box 69, Folder 1)
    Author: American Labor Archive and Research Institute, Inc.
- American Labor Associates, Publication (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: American Labor Associates, 1932; Publication (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Next steps in radicalism, an outline, 1932; Publication (Box 69, Folder 2)
- International Labor Organization, Publication (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Labor's stake in Bretton Woods, 1945; Publication (Box 69, Folder 3)
    Author: Broadus Mitchell
  - Item 2: What the workers expect of the International Labor Organization, 1944; Publication (Box 69, Folder 3)
    Author: Bernardo Iban~ez Aguila
- American Labor Education Service, Publication (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: A labor school on world affairs, Publication (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Africa, Publication (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: American labor Education Service Bulletin, 1953; Publication (Box 69, Folder 4)
    Notes: 1953 January
  - Item 4: American labor Education Service Bulletin, 1955; Publication (Box 69, Folder 4)
    Notes: 1955 July
  - Item 5: American labor Education Service Bulletin, 1956; Publication (Box 69, Folder 4)
    Notes: 1956 July
  - Item 6: American labor Education Service Bulletin, 1957; Publication (Box 69, Folder 4)
    Notes: 1957 December
  - Item 7: American labor Education Service Bulletin, 1958; Publication (Box 69, Folder 4)
    Notes: 1958 December
  - Item 8: American labor Education Service Bulletin, 1959; Publication (Box 69, Folder 4)
    Notes: 1959 July
  - Item 9: American labor Education Service Bulletin, 1960; Publication (Box 69, Folder 4)
    Notes: 1960 July
  - Item 10: Group work in the workers' education setting, Publication (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - Item 11: History of an idea, Publication (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - Item 12: Jobs in workers education, Publication (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - Item 13: Labor scholarships abroad, Publication (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - Item 14: Labor unions educate, Publication (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - Item 15: New goals for labor education, Publication (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - Item 16: Selected references on the White Collar Worker, Publication (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - Item 17: The American Labor Education Service, Publication (Box 69, Folder 4)
    Author: Eleanor G. Coit
  - Item 18: The right to security, Publication (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - Item 19: Unionists are urged: get message across, Publication (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - Item 20: Unionists lift community sights, Publication (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - Item 21: Aging and the aged: annotated bibliography for use in labor education, 1959; Publication (Box 69, Folder 4)
    Author: American Labor Eduation Service
  - Item 22: Early experiments in workers' education, Publication (Box 69, Folder 4)
    Author: Amy Hewes
  - Item 23: miscellaneous correspondence and memos, Publication (Box 69, Folder 4)
- American Labor Health Association, Publication (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Members handbook: how to use your health and welfare services, Publication (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: The physician and labor health plans, Publication (Box 69, Folder 5)
    Author: American Labor Health Association
  - Item 3: Your right to medical care; how unions may ensure it, Publication (Box 69, Folder 5)
- American Labor Party, Publication (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Program of the American Labor Party, Publication (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Why I believe that the future belongs to labor, Publication (Box 70, Folder 1)
    Author: Hendrik Willem Van Loon
  - Item 3: Second Annual Ball of the American Labor Party, Kings County, 1939; Publication (Box 70, Folder 1)
    Author: American Labor Party
    Notes: Program
  - Item 4: Thomas E. Dewey, Labor's candidate for District Attorney, Publication (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Vote for James Gilman the American LaborCandidate, Publication (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: Issues of "American Labor Post"; copy of "Labor Party Herald", 1937; Publication (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: Tickets to Madison Square Garden Rally for the American Labor Party, Publication (Box 70, Folder 1)
- American Labor Research Institute (New York, N.Y.), Publication (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: American Labor Research Institute: clearing house for material on labor, 1946; Publication (Box 70, Folder 2)
    Author: American Labor Research Institute (New York, N.Y.)
- American Labor Research Institute (New York, N.Y.), Publication (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: American Labor and the United Nations, 1957; Publication (Box 70, Folder 3)
- American Labor Research Institute (New York, N.Y.), Publication (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: American Labor World, 1919; Publication (Box 70, Folder 4)
    Notes: vol.20:no.4 (1919)
- American Labor Research Institute (New York, N.Y.), Publication (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Negro Champion, 1925; Publication (Box 70, Folder 5)
    Notes: (July 1925)
  - Item 2: Press releases, 1925; Publication (Box 70, Folder 5)
    Notes: (Aug. 1925) (Sept. 1925)
- National Trade Union Emergency Conference for Labor Palestine, Publication (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Israel, the beginning of hope, Publication (Box 70, Folder 6)
    Author: Al J. Hayes
  - Item 2: Proceedings of the National Trade Union Emergency Conference for Labor Palestine. May 16, 17, 18, 1947, Atlantic City, N.J., Publication (Box 70, Folder 6)
    Author: National Trade Union Emergency Conference for Labor Palestine (1947: Atlantic City)
- American White Collar League, Publication (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: American White Collar League, A resume of the plans and purposes of the league, Publication (Box 70, Folder 7)
- Miscellaneous publications, Publication (Box 70, Folder 8)